A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the State Coordinator of the Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 1987-2013
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files (Acc. 53598), 1995-2013.
  - Instructions from the Secretary of Public Safety Office, undated. (Box 17)
  - VCU Performance Emergency Group - VEI, CMI, etc. to Secretary of Public Safety, 1999-2001. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Contract procurement requests, 2009. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Contract procurement requests, 2008. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Contract procurement requests, 2009. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Hiring request forms, 2003-2013. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2013 Nov-Dec. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2013 Sept-Oct. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2013 July-Aug. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2013 May-June. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2013 Mar-Apr. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2013 Jan-Feb. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2012 Nov-Dec. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2012 Sept-Oct. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2012 July-Aug. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2012 May-June. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2012 Mar-Apr. (Box 17)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Weekly reports, 2012 Jan-Feb. (Box 17)
  - Briefing to Secretary Aronholt on Emergency/Disaster Response, 1998 Jan. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Productivity savings, 2000. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Decision briefs, 2012-2013. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Decision briefs, 2010-2011. (Box 18)
  - Agency Preparedness Assessment - VAHS formerly OCP, undated. (Box 18)
  - Coordinator Preparedness Reports - Governor / Cabinet Secretaries, 2012-2013. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Richmond Metro Senios Officials Hurrican Preparedness meeting, 2007 June 28. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - State Stat reports, 2011-2013. (Box 18)
  - Constituent draft responses for Governor / Secretary of Public Safety / VDEM, 2013. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2012 Aug-Dec. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2012 Jan-July. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2011. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2010. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2009. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2008. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2006. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 2005. (Box 18)
  - Secretary of Public Safety - Constituent inquiries, 20. (Box 18)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Jan. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Feb. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Mar. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Apr. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 May. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 June. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 July. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Aug. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Sept. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Oct. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Nov. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2003 Dec. (Box 19)
  - Correspondence - Assistant State Coordinator of Administration, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Finance Division, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - IFLOWS Supervisor, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Preparedness and Mitigation Division, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Public Information Office, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Recovery and Administrative Services, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Technological Hazards Division, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Accounts, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Virginia Code Commission, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Commission on Local Government, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Criminal Justice Services, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Emergency Medical Services, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Environmental Quality, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Fire Programs, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Forestry, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Health, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Information Technology, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Mines, Mineral and Energy, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Virginia State Library, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Virginia State Police, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Transportation, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Army, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) National Emergency Training Center, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2000 May-June. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2000 July-Aug. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2000 Sept-Oct. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 2000 Nov-Dec. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) Project, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Small Business Administration, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Justice - Office for State and Local Domestic Preparedness Support, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Transportation, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Civil Air Patrol, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Council of Governors, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Damn Safety, 2000. (Box 20)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Jan. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Feb. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Mar. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Apr. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 May. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 June. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 July. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Aug. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Sept. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Oct. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Nov. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2001 Dec. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Jan. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Feb. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Mar. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Apr. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 May. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 June. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 July. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Aug. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Sept. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Oct. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Nov. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2002 Dec. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Jan. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Feb. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Mar. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Apr. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 May. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 June. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 July. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Aug. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Sept. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Oct. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Nov. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2003 Dec. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Jan. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Feb. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Mar. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Apr. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 May. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 June. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 July. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Aug. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Sept. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Oct. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Nov. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 2004 Dec. (Box 21)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Accounts, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Army, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Aviation, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Commission on Local Government, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Criminal Justice, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Education, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Environmental Quality, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Fire Programs, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Forestry, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of General Services, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Health, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Human Resource Management, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia National Guard, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of the State Internal Auditor, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Library of Virginia, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Social Services, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia State Police, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Transportation, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Small Business Administration, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Transportation, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Justice, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - American Red Cross, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Civil Air Patrol, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Commonwealth Commuter Choice Program Ridefinder, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia Drought Monitoring Task Force, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia Marine Resources Commission, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Military Affairs, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Virginia State Police, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Transportation, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Finance Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Personnel Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Management Information Systems Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Operations Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Preparedness and Mitigation Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Public Affairs Office, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Recovery and Administrative Services Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Public Assistance Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Regional Offices, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Technological Hazards Division, 2001. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Accounts, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Council on Information Management, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Conservation and Recreation, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Corrections, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Emergency Medical Services, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Fire Programs, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of General Services, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Information Technologies, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Division of Legislative Services, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Technological Hazards Division, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Council on Governments, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Housing and Community Development, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Correspondence - Dept. of Army, 2002. (Box 22)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - ACAMS grant application, 2008. (Box 23)
  - COVA EOP Family Assistance Center Plan, 2013. (Box 23)
  - COOP correspondence, 2002-2013. (Box 23)
  - Delmarva Hurricane Evacuation Study, 2002. (Box 23)
  - Dominion Energy, 2002-2013. (Box 23)
  - EVA COVA Entity User Accounts Report, 2006-2013. (Box 23)
  - Emergency Alert System, 2003. (Box 23)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 2003. (Box 23)
  - Grant Non-Supplanting Certificate, 2007-2011. (Box 23)
  - DHS HSGP Administrative Plan, 2012. (Box 23)
  - DHA HSGP, 2010-2013. (Box 23)
  - DHS HSGP, 2007-2009. (Box 23)
  - HSG Audits, 2010-2014. (Box 23)
  - US Dept. of Homeland Security - Office of Domestic Preparedness, 2003-2004. (Box 23)
  - Dept. of Homeland Security - Office of Grants and Training, 2003-2004. (Box 23)
  - HSG Stateholder meeting, 2006. (Box 23)
  - Limited Exemption of Hours Worked Emergency Declarations, 2010-2011. (Box 23)
  - Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, 2003. (Box 23)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Comments, requests and surveys, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Conferences, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Reports and requests, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Response and Recovery Committee, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Surveys, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Various committee information, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - National Incident Management System (NIMS) - Compliance decision paper, 2007. (Box 23)
  - National Weather Service, 2002. (Box 23)
  - Southern Governor's Compact, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - Southern Governor's Association, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - Statewide Mutual Aid, 2002-2003. (Box 23)
  - SWaM Procurement Plan, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - Technical Assistance: Preparedness Program Management, 2007-2009. (Box 23)
  - Unistar Nuclear Energy, undated. (Box 23)
  - Urban Area Security Initiative grants, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - Virginia Association of Broadcasters, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Donated Funds Management Committee, 2002, 2004. (Box 23)
  - Virginia Emergency Management Symposium, 2008-2014. (Box 23)
  - Virginia Hurricane Evacuation Re-Study, undated. (Box 23)
  - Virginia Infrastructure Physical Security Enhancement Program, 2002-2014. (Box 23)
  - Weather Radia Transmitter grant, 2007-2008. (Box 23)
  - Citizen Corps (CERT), 2004, 2005, 2007. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Finance Division, 2002-2003. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Human Resource Recognition Committee, undated. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - iFLOWS, 2002. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Operations Division, 2002-2003. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Public Affairs Office, 2002. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Recovery and Administrative Services Division, 2002-2003. (Box 23)
  - VDEM - Technological Hazards Division, 2002-2003. (Box 23)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2013. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2012. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2011. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2010. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2009. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2007. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2006. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2005. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2004. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety / Governor, 2003 Jan-June. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety / Governor, 2003 July-Dec. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Governor / COOP activities, 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2002 Jan-Apr. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Chronological, 2002 May-Dec. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Public Safety, 2002. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Coordinator with Governor / Secretary, 2002. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Secretary of Administration, 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Contracts / Procurement, 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Other States (miscellaneous), 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Individual Virginia state agencies (miscellaneous), 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Other federal agencies, 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Commerce, 2002-2007. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Energy, 2008-2013. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, 2002-2014. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services, 2003. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Homeland Security, 2003-2013. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. Justice, 2002-2014. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 2006-2012. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 2002-2005. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Small Business Administration, 2002-2014. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Small Business Administration - Disaster requests, 2006. (Box 24)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Dept. of Transportation, 2002-2014. (Box 24)
  - Amateur Radio letters, undated. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2001. (Box 25)
  - Radio Amateur Civil Emergency Services, 2001. (Box 25)
  - Randy Corps Study National Guard, undated. (Box 25)
  - Regional Response Program, 1997. (Box 25)
  - Southern States Energy Board, 1997. (Box 25)
  - Spill Prevention and Response Program, undated. (Box 25)
  - Statewide Agency Radio System Users Group, undated. (Box 25)
  - Virginia National Guard, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Public Inquiry System, 2002. (Box 25)
  - Virginia Power Company, 2002. (Box 25)
  - Fire Chiefs Assosciation of Virginia, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Citizen Corps (CERT), 2003. (Box 25)
  - Employee Transportation Committee, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Geographic Information System Advisory Group, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Hampton Roads Emergency Management Committee, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Mediation Project, 1995. (Box 25)
  - National Governor's Association, 2000. (Box 25)
  - National USR Response System Advisory Committee, 2001. (Box 25)
  - National Weather Service, 2000. (Box 25)
  - New Partnerip Commission, 2000. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2000 May-June. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2000 July-Aug. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2000 Sept-Oct. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association, 2000 Nov-Dec. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Strategic Plan, 2000. (Box 25)
  - National Emergency Management Association - Legal Counsel Committee, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Accident Review Committee, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Budget, 2000. (Box 25)
  - Regional Office - Region III, 2002. (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous general correspondence, 2004. (Box 25)